So my name is Keanu Pahio. I'm one of the
developer of the KERI Foundation and my
presentation today was about deploying
KERI infrastructure. So including
witnesses, watchers, and the wallet. I
think it's about making connections
together. So through my presentation, we
can see how you can deploy both watchers,
witnesses, and also the wallet, but also
the boot server that we developed and how
it all works together and how this
infrastructure is relevant for a
production or also development
environment. I think it would lose the
connection and how it all works together,
how it's related. And I think it's a good
step for beginners because it's really
easy to understand. So I think new people
who come into KERI could benefit. So if we
lose it, it might be harder for people to
get into it. I think it's really easy to
understand.